Amanda Steele Show.
Comedian DC Young Fly was recently booed off stage.
Let's just take a listen, y'all.
That's what is going on.
I mean, despite the negative reaction,
he encouraged the audience to stay strong and stay in the face,
you know, stay strong in the face of adversity and to keep God close.
You know, I think what he's realizing in this actual moment is like,
oh, it's time to go in another direction.
Like, this isn't the space for me no more.
I mean, he lost his wife, his girl, you know,
who's the mother of his children, and then many people blame him.
So that's a guilt that you would carry.
Also, you know, he never really grieved.
He kept working.
And that's something that so many folks just don't do.
They don't get a chance oftentimes to even stop to grieve, right?
Like, I don't know that Kanye would be where he's now
if he had been able to stop to grieve.
But I also just am always just amazed at the lack of compassion that people have.
I just felt sorry.
I have to hit him up because I really do want to pour into him.
And I think, you know, Black audiences in these particular type of comedy shows,
they really expect a joke every eight seconds.
And if you're not giving them a joke every eight seconds,
they really write you off.
But I got to ask y'all.
Because we have to treat each other with the same compassion and empathy
that we demand from those outside of the community.
All right.
We'll be right back to The Amanda Seal Show.
We are, we are, we are.